Guide to the Records of the 7th Regiment 1767-1983 (bulk 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Headquarters, 1767-1972, 13040
  - Subseries 4: Board of Officers and Committees, 1833-1949, 13237
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1870-1879; 13274 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1880-1889; 13273 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1897-1898; 13272 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1900-1909; 13271 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Board of Officers- Treasurer's Reports, 1910-1917; 13270 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Board of Officers- Reports of the Trustees of the 7th Regiment Armory Building, 1897-1913; 13269 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Board of Officers- Paymaster Reports, 1852-1905; 13268 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Board of Officers- Reports of the Secretary, 1851-1856; 13267 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Armory Committee- Reports, 1863-1889; 13266 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - The Armory Committee- Reports, 1894-1899; 13265 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - The Armory Committee- Reports, 1900-1905; 13264 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - The Armory Committee- Reports, 1906-1926; 13263 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Committee on the Awards of the Cross of Honor- Reports, 1854-1920; 13262 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Library and Arts Committee- Reports, 1880-1917; 13261 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Committees on Uniforms and Dress- Reports, 1853-1919; 13260 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the State of the Regiment, 1872-1894; 13259 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Music Committee- Reports, 1859; 13258 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee- Reports, 1857-1919; 13257 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - General Committee on New Armory- Reports, Resolutions, Circulars, 1873-1880; 13256 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Special Committee- Reports, Undated; 13255 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Special Committee- Reports, 1825-1869; 13254 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Special Committee- Reports, 1870-1889; 13253 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Special Committee- Reports, 1890-1912; 13252 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, "Battalion Minutes- National Guard", 1825-1830; 13251 (Volume 42)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1830-1835; 13250 (Volume 43)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1835-1844; 13249 (Volume 44)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1844-1851; 13248 (Volume 45)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1852-1858; 13247 (Volume 46)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1858-1862; 13246 (Volume 47)
    - Minute Book, Board of Officers, 1832-1870; 13245 (Volume 48)
    - Minute Book, Minutes of the Board for the Examination of Officers and Non-Commissioned Officers, 1869-1876; 13244 (Volume 49)
    - Board of Examination Record, 1876-1880; 13243 (Volume 50)
    - Minutes of Council of Officers, 1858 Apr.-1860 Mar.; 13242 (Volume 51)
    - Account Book for the Board of Officers, Fines, 1863-1867; 13241 (Volume 52)
    - Council of Officers Roster, 1849-1862; 13240 (Volume 53)
    - Personnel Roll Book of Board (Council) of Officers, 1858-1860; 13239 (Volume 54)
    - Minute Book, Committee on Reception and Inaugural Ball, 1880; 13238 (Volume 55)
  - Subseries 5: Personnel, 1819-1953, 13185
    This subseries includes regimental rosters, rolls, returns, enrollment lists and certificates, and attendance reports. Much of the loose material relates to the Civil War, especially printed lists (booklets, newspapers and posters) of New York City recruits and draftees. Also included in this subseries are lists of 7th Regiment war dead from the First and Second World Wars and the Korean War. Bound volumes in this subseries are muster rolls, roll books, and rosters.
    For rosters of individual 7th Regiment companies, see Series II (especially Bound Volumes), and the Veterans of the 7th Regiment files in this series, Subseries 10.
    - Enlistment Certificates, Commissions, 1819-1832; 13236 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Resignation/ Discharge Certificates, 1826-1828, 1874-1895; 13235 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Muster roll, list, 1827, undated; 13234 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Civil War Recruits, donors, 1861; 13233 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Roster, 1862; 13232 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Enrollment Lists- 9th, 15th, 16th, 18th, 20th, 21st Wards, 1863; 13231 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Enrollment Posters- 1st, 6th Wards (lists of names), [1863]; 13230 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Captain's Returns, 1863; 13229 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - NY Daily Transcript Extra- List of names, 9th Ward, 1865 Jan. 5; 13228 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - NY Daily Transcript Extra- List of names, 16th Ward, 1865 Jan. 9; 13227 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Guard of Honor, President Lincoln's Body, [1865]; 13226 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Roll of honor, Civil War, 1866; 13225 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rolls, Printed, 1868-1909; 13224 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Rosters, 1883-1884, 1901-1904, 1906, 1908; 13223 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - List of Officers, National Guard, 1912; 13222 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Mexican Border Service- Returns, rolls, 1916; 13221 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Roll of Honor, 1919; 13220 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - War Dead, 1919-1953, undated; 13219 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Attendance Reports, 1937-1938; 13218 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Monthly Rosters, various divisions, Undated; 13217 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Blank forms, 1944; 13216 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 13215 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Certificates, Rolls Enlistment and appointment certificates. Includes several certificates for William H. Kipp (1857-1908). Also rolls for 11th Reg. (1806-1820), Battery F (1940) and Exempt Members (1860-1863, 1910-1914)., 1806-1940; 13214 (Box 88 (oversize))
    - Personnel Roll Book, 1847; 13213 (Volume 56)
    - Muster Rolls, 1861-1863 (1904 copy); 13212 (Volume 57)
    - Furlough Book, 1862; 13211 (Volume 58)
    - Muster Rolls, Civil War, 1862; 13210 (Volume 59)
    - Officer's 7th Regiment Roll Book, 1866-1880; 13209 (Volume 60)
    - Roster of the 7th Regiment NGSNY, 1862 June-1899 May; 13208 (Volume 61)
    - 7th Regiment Rosters, 1872-1910; 13207 (Volume 62)
    - 7th Regiment Rosters, 1889-1919; 13206 (Volume 63)
    - Volunteer Battery Roster, 1891-1892; 13205 (Volume 64)
    - Rosters, 1883-1908; 13204 (Volume 65)
    - Roll Book, 1916-1917; 13203 (Volume 66)
    - Muster Rolls, 1871-1874; 13202 (Volume 67)
    - Muster Rolls, 1875-1878; 13201 (Volume 68)
    - Muster Rolls, 1879-1885; 13200 (Volume 69)
    - Muster Rolls, 1886-1889; 13199 (Volume 70)
    - Muster Rolls, 1890-1893; 13198 (Volume 71)
    - Muster Rolls, 1894-1897; 13197 (Volume 72)
    - Muster Rolls, 1898-1900; 13196 (Volume 73)
    - Muster Rolls, 1901, 1902, 1904; 13195 (Volume 74)
    - Muster Rolls, 1905, 1907; 13194 (Volume 75)
    - Muster Rolls, 1908-1911; 13193 (Volume 76)
    - Muster Rolls, 1912-1914; 13192 (Volume 77)
    - Muster Rolls, 1917-1919; 13191 (Volume 78)
    - Muster Rolls, 1919-1923; 13190 (Volume 79)
    - Muster Rolls, 1924-1929; 13189 (Volume 80)
    - Muster Rolls, 1865-1870; 13188 (Volume 81)
    - Personnel Roster, 1867; 13187 (Volume 82)
    - World War I Dead, 1917-1918; 13186 (Volume 83)
  - Subseries 6: Financial Documents, 1852-1946, 13164
    The financial material contains annual reports, account books, material related to pay and insurance, and a large number of bills and receipts. For further financial information see the Treasurer's Reports in the Board of Officers subseries.
    - Annual Reports, 1863-1883; 13184 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Accounts, Bills, Receipts, Undated; 13183 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Accounts, Bills, Receipts, 1859-1866; 13182 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Accounts, Bills, Receipts, 1874-1936; 13181 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Sample copies of Payroll and W-2 Forms, 1946; 13180 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Pay rates for various rankings, Undated; 13179 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Inventories of Supplies, 1861, undated; 13178 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Insurance Policies, 1908-1910; 13177 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Assessments, 1852; 13176 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Account Book, 1830-1833; 13175 (Volume 84)
    - Account Book, Officer's Accounts, 1833-1841; 13174 (Volume 85)
    - Account Book, Officer's Accounts, 1850; 13173 (Volume 86)
    - Account Book, Officer's Accounts, 1844-1853; 13172 (Volume 87)
    - Account Book, Officer's Accounts, 1853-1860; 13171 (Volume 87-A)
    - Account Book, Members' Accounts, 1874-1878; 13170 (Volume 88)
    - Account Book, Quartermaster's Book, 1862; 13169 (Volume 89)
    - Account Book, Cash Book, 1880-1892; 13168 (Volume 90)
    - Cash Book, 1862; 13167 (Volume 91)
    - Expense Book, 1833-1861; 13166 (Volume 92)
    - Record Book, Regiment Board of Auditors, 1863-1864; 13165 (Volume 93)
  - Subseries 7: Legal, 1848-1927, 13148
    The legal material of the 7th Regiment consists mainly of court martials but also includes wills, testimonies, transcripts of court proceeding, acts, and affidavits. There are some court martials from the Headquarters of the Army and the First Brigade, New York State Artillery.
    - Armory Independent Cadets- Court Martial Orders, 1861; 13163 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Will of Mary B. Lane, 1912-1915; 13162 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Deponent's Testimonies, 1849, 1866; 13161 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Affidavits, 1873; 13160 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Consent to Parade, 1876; 13159 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Acts and Laws, 1873-1901; 13158 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - United States Naval Institute Proceedings- "Security by Enactment", 1848; 13157 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Art Appraisals, [1870]; 13156 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Headquarters of the Army- Court Martials, 1891-1893; 13155 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - First Brigade, New York State Artillery- Court Martials, 1831-1833; 13154 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Minutes of the Meetings of Court Martials, 1876-1877; 13153 (Volume 94)
    - Court martial Book, "Return of Delinquents", 1860-1863; 13152 (Volume 95)
    - Material re Artemus B. Johnson vs. Emmons Clark, NY Supreme Court, 1869; 13151 (Volume 96)
    - Material re The People ex. rel. Cheesman vs. Clark, 1878; 13150 (Volume 97)
    - Proceedings of Examining Board, 1927; 13149 (Volume 98)
  - Subseries 8: Training Material, 1868-1953, 13134
    This subseries contains manuals, pamphlets, handouts, exercises, and notes related to specific regimental training. Many of the materials are related to controlling riots.
    - "Critical Point Security Plan of Operation 1943 Test", 13147 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Course Reference for Course "A"- Basic Course in "Handling Personnel," includes supervisor's and foreman's handbook, 1939; 13146 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "Personal Behavior and Basic Tactics in Riot Control", 1974 June; 13145 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "Notes on Riot Duty", 1944 Dec.; 13144 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "Notes on Riot Duty", 1944 Dec.; 13143 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 107th Infantry- Tactical School, 1947 Feb., 1947 April; 13142 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "Manual for the Loading and Firing the Remington Breech-Loading Rifle", 1872; 13141 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "March Discipline and Traffic Control" with Notebook of George Nichols, 1918; 13140 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - General Training Notes and Exercises, 1944-1949; 13139 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 7th Regiment Manual, 1868; 13138 (Volume 99)
    - 7th Regiment Manual, 1868; 13137 (Volume 100)
    - Field Notebook, US Engineering Department, 1953; 13136 (Volume 101)
    - Field Notebook, US Engineering Department, 1953; 13135 (Volume 102)
  - Subseries 9: Report Books, 1814-1921, 13110
    The report books are records of attendance of members of each company present at drills, parades, or practices.
    - Report Book- 11th Regiment (Returns and Requisitions), 1814; 13133 (Volume 103)
    - Report Book- 11th Regiment, 1814; 13132 (Volume 104)
    - Report Book- North Battery, Guard Report/Garrison Report, 1814; 13131 (Volume 105)
    - Report Book- Morning Reports, Fort Federal Hill, Maryland, 1862; 13130 (Volume 106)
    - Report Book- Report of the 7th Regiment Celebration, 1862; 13129 (Volume 107)
    - Report Book- 7th Regiment Daily Report, 1883; 13128 (Volume 108)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Report Book, 1886; 13127 (Volume 109)
    - Report Book- 2nd Battalion, 7th Regiment, Camp Abrams Ridgewood Car Stables, 1895; 13126 (Volume 110)
    - Report Book- Camp Abrams, Brooklyn, 1895; 13125 (Volume 111)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Report Book, 1909-1911; 13124 (Volume 112)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1911-1912; 13123 (Volume 113)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1912 Oct.-1912 Dec.; 13122 (Volume 114)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1913-1914; 13121 (Volume 115)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1914; 13120 (Volume 116)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1915; 13119 (Volume 117)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1916 Jan.-1916 July; 13118 (Volume 118)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1916 July-1916 Sept.; 13117 (Volume 119)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1917 Jan.-1917 July; 13116 (Volume 120)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1917-1918; 13115 (Volume 121)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1918-1919; 13114 (Volume 122)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1919-1920; 13113 (Volume 123)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1920-1921; 13112 (Volume 124)
    - Report Book- Consolidated Morning Report, 1921; 13111 (Volume 125)
  - Subseries 10: Veterans Material, 1859-1972, 13079
    This subseries primarily contains material for various veterans associations including Veterans of the 7th Regiment, Society of the War Veterans, and Veterans of the National Guard. The bulk of the Veterans of the 7th Regiment material is files from the 1940s containing correspondence and company rosters. Correspondence consists mostly of letters from veterans to William B. Miles, Secretary of the Veterans of the 7th Regiment, many of which discuss their recent activities, their service in the 7th, and include information about other 7th members. There are numerous V-Mails. Veterans of the 7th Regiment material also includes nineteenth-century orders, circulars, reports, and by-laws, and bulletins from the 1940s-1960s. Society of War Veterans and Veterans of the National Guard material includes records books, correspondence, minutes, circulars, and printed items. Two minute books of the Veterans Military Rifle Association of New York City are also found in this subseries.
    See also Series IX for Veterans ephemera.
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Orders, Circulars, Notices, 1871-1893, undated; 13109 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Reports, By-Laws, 1882-1892; 13108 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Members, Circulars, 1910-1924; 13107 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, 1942-1943; 13106 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, 1944; 13105 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, 1945 Jan.-1945 June; 13104 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, 1945 July-1945 Dec.; 13103 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, 1946-1948; 13102 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Correspondence, Undated; 13101 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Chain Letters/Rosters, [1942-1947]; 13100 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Company Rosters, A-F, [1942-1947]; 13099 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Company Rosters, G-I, [1942-1947]; 13098 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Company Rosters, K-M, [1942-1947]; 13097 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Company Rosters/Other, [1942-1947]; 13096 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Rosters, Batteries A-G, Unidentified, [1941-1947]; 13095 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Other Material, [1942-1947]; 13094 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Bulletins, 1948-1970; 13093 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Veterans of the 7th Regiment- Form Letters, 1950-1956; 13092 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Society of the War Veterans- Correspondence, Minutes, 1884-1935, 1972; 13091 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Society of the War Veterans- Circulars, 1885-1939, undated; 13090 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Society of the War Veterans- Printed Material, 1866-1911; 13089 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Veterans of the National Guard Material, 1859-1879; 13088 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Veterans Material- William L. Darling, William A. Darling, 1868-1920; 13087 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Veterans Material- General J. Fred Pierson, 13086 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Veterans Material- Other, 1861, undated; 13085 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Record Book, Society of War Veterans, 1883-1899; 13084 (Volume 126)
    - Record Book, Society of War Veterans, 1899-1921; 13083 (Volume 127)
    - Constitution, Society of War Veterans, [1880-1890]; 13082 (Volume 128)
    - Minute Book, Veteran Military Rifle Association of NYC, 1914-1927; 13081 (Volume 129)
    - Minute Book, Veteran Military Rifle Association of NYC, 1932; 13080 (Volume 130)
  - Subseries 11: Administrative, 1767-1943, 13041
    This subseries contains other material related to the regiment that does not fit into the above subseries. It includes press releases, documents regarding the regiment's bill of dress, emergency plans, etc.
    - Bill of Dress of the 7th Regiment, 1869; 13078 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 7th Regiment Press Releases, [1920-1940]; 13077 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 7th Regiment Emergency Plan, 1944; 13076 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Address and Telephone Directories, Undated; 13075 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Lists of Names and Committees, 1881-1882, 1943, undated; 13074 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Lists of Items and Regiment Members at Camp Clinton, [1831]; 13073 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - First Battalion, List of Names and Addresses, Undated; 13072 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Passes for Soldiers, 1861-1862; 13071 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Family Record of Lt. Forrester, [1888]; 13070 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Lists of Railroads and Roads, [1891]; 13069 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Third Brigade- Resolution, 1877; 13068 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Adjutant's Book, [1820-1851]; 13067 (Volume 131)
    - Adjutant's Book, 1871, 1877, 1889; 13066 (Volume 132)
    - Adjutant's Report re: Brooklyn Trolley Strike, 1895 Jan.; 13065 (Volume 133)
    - Commissioned Officers Oath Book, 1859-1860; 13064 (Volume 134)
    - Commissioned Officers Oath Book, 1859-1864; 13063 (Volume 135)
    - 7th Regiment Minutes, 1813-1815; 13062 (Volume 136)
    - Minute Book, Order of Business Non-Commissioned Association, 1866-1885; 13061 (Volume 137)
    - Speeches of Colonel Appleton and Chauncey M. De Pew, 1903; 13060 (Volume 138)
    - Speeches of Colonel Appleton, 1903 Apr. 15; 13059 (Volume 139)
    - Guard and Surgeon's Reports, 1862; 13058 (Volume 140)
    - Consolidated Monthly Report, 1867-1880; 13057 (Volume 141)
    - Reports, 69th Battalion, Report on Service in Brooklyn, 1895; 13056 (Volume 142)
    - Report on Service in Brooklyn, 1895; 13055 (Volume 143)
    - Quartermaster's Reports, 1895 Dec. 31; 13054 (Volume 144)
    - Report of Medical Department on Service in Brooklyn, 1895; 13053 (Volume 145)
    - Endorsement Book, 1870-1879; 13052 (Volume 146)
    - Endorsement Book, 1880-1885; 13051 (Volume 147)
    - Seventh Regiment Rhymes, [1905]; 13050 (Volume 148)
    - Seventh Regiment Rhymes, 1905; 13049 (Volume 149)
    - Remarks Upon Regimental Discipline, 1767; 13048 (Volume 150)
    - Minute Book, 7th Regiment Exempt Association, 1859-1867; 13047 (Volume 151)
    - Guard Book, Camp Cameron, Washington, DC, 1861; 13046 (Volume 152)
    - By-Laws of the 7th Regiment Association, 1866-1890; 13045 (Volume 153)
    - Directory of the 7th Regiment, 1872 Jan. 1; 13044 (Volume 154)
    - Manual for the Mountain Howitzer (Manuscript), 1872; 13043 (Volume 155)
    - Autograph Book, Camp of Instruction, Peekskill, NY, 1889; 13042 (Volume 156)
- Series II: Companies, 1806-1949, 12788
  This series contains material directly related to the companies of the 7th Regiment. Material includes rosters and roll books, orders, resolutions, by-laws, enlistment records, correspondence, memos, reports, financial records, circulars, record books, minutes, notices, and a few photographs. The bulk of the material is for companies B and F.
  Major portions of this series include approximately two boxes of enlistment records, especially for Co. B, (1939-1949), which contain basic biographic information, and sometimes health information, for 7th members and potential members. Co. F. material includes the company's World War I files: orders, memos, bulletins, and schedules that discuss appointments, inspection instructions, health matters, marching and behavioral discipline, food, postal regulations, enforcement of attire regulations, and various procedures.
  Note: the 7th Regiment initially designated companies by number, not letter. This practice continued even after the letter system was instituted; therefore, for example, Co. B and 2nd Company are the same. There is no Company J.
  For other material relating to 7th Regiment companies, see rosters [c1942-1947] in the Veterans of the 7th Regiment files, Series I (Subseries 10). See also Series IX for ephemera (bulk Co. B), and Series XIV: Visual Materials for oversized items and photo albums relating to companies.
  - Box and Folder:, 12940
    - Co. A, 1826-1892; 13039 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Co. A: "Att-A-Boy" newsletter, 1917 Sept. 22-Oct. 16; 13038 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, A-Bi, 1939-1949; 13037 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Bl-Bu, 1939-1949; 13036 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ca, 1939-1949; 13035 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ch-De, 1939-1949; 13034 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Di-Fl, 1939-1949; 13033 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Fo-Gi, 1939-1949; 13032 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Gl-Ha, 1939-1949; 13031 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, He-J, 1939-1949; 13030 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, K, 1939-1949; 13029 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, L, 1939-1949; 13028 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ma-Me, 1939-1949; 13027 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Mi-My, 1939-1949; 13026 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, N-R, 1939-1949; 13025 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, S, 1939-1949; 13024 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, T-V, 1939-1949; 13023 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, W-Z, 1939-1949; 13022 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: "Fordham & Poly Preps Recruit Applications", 1946; 13021 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Information Form, Former Members, 1946; 13020 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - [Co. B]: Correspondence--Recruitment--[G. Richard Ludlow, Capt.], 1940; 13019 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Rosters, 1842, 1902-1907, 1945-1946; 13018 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Register of Members (2 copies), 1864-1910; 13017 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Orders, 1835-1909; 13016 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Co. B: Resolutions, 1858-1892; 13015 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members--Correspondence, 1890-1911; 13014 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members--By-Laws, Resolutions, 1891-1896, undated; 13013 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members, 1900-1917; 13012 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Memos, 1944, 1947; 13011 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Reports, 1941; 13010 (Box 18, Folder 5)